An AI agent is controlling this PC —
from another machine.
One command turns a Windows box
into an MCP server:  npx winreach-mcp
It opens a secure Cloudflare tunnel —
no inbound firewall holes.
Any MCP agent connects over HTTP
with its own bearer key.
Run real PowerShell, remotely —
as a single MCP tool call.
Move files both ways —
sandboxed and hash-verified.
Capture the screen
whenever the agent needs to look.
And drive the mouse and keyboard
like a human — full computer use.
Every agent gets its own key and role:
admin · operator · readonly.
A regex command policy blocks
dangerous commands — live.
And every action is written
to an append-only audit log.
WinReach — give your AI agent
its own Windows machine.